<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[When you care enough to send the very best]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[When you care enough to send the very best]]></description>
        <link>http://creektransport.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 14:08:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://creektransport.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 14:08:23 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We at Creek General Transport … give our customers our greatest attention full of our core values, we believe that our customer satisfaction will always maintain our old reputation in the transportation business in UAE.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7171a092-9368-44f1-8630-82613e306ac5.jpg" title="Creek General Transport Loves their customers">,<h1>We at Creek General Transport … give our customers our greatest attention full of our core values, we believe that our customer satisfaction will always maintain our old reputation in the transportation business in UAE.</h1>,<h2>LACNOR</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/065f0bf8-9366-4db7-9dba-073de43654ae.png" title="LACNOR">,<p>LACNOR is a part of National Food Products Company engaged in the manufacturing of fruit juices and dairy products since 1978. Creek having very good relationship with them and working together from 1990 onwards for the transportation of Juices, Milk Powder, Fruit Pulp, Tetra packs etc.</p>,<h2>Emirates Lube Oil Company (ELCO)</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f4dea731-d6c2-4b82-a281-34d3412fb38c.png" title="ELCO">,<p>Based in Sharjah, UAE is an ISO 9002, ISO 14001 company which commenced operations in 1972. ELCO is one of the largest lubricants manufacturing and marketing companies in the Middle East. Creek is working with them past 30 years engaged in Bulk Base Oil &amp; Bitumen tanker deliveries all over UAE</p>,<h2>Shankar Trading Company -The Giant Group</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4fd73a6b-e2cd-454a-a9c0-e3f475f152f9.png" title="GIANT" alt=" ">,<p>Started as wholesaler of food stuff in 1985. Today it has diversified businesses with interests in Supermarkets, Wholesale, Distribution, Retail and Manufacturing of FMCG and other consumer goods.</p>,<h2>Richmond Mercantile</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a5fc02a7-4c84-4de6-ae66-424056a4c8e9.png" title="Richmond Mercantile" alt="
">,<p>The Richmond Group is an international business group of manufacturing and trading companies headquartered in the UAE with offices in Australia, China, India, Oman, and Singapore.</p>,<p>CGT is providing fleet of vehicles towards transportation of Bulk &amp; Packed Bitumen, Asphalt Products such as Bitumen/ Asphalt binders and polymer modified Bitumen (PMB), cutbacks and emulsions.</p>,<h2>Techno Lube</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/190af234-a4e6-4c63-b554-66bebffa3c76.png" title="Techno Lube">,<p>A sister concern of Petromin Corporation KSA, a joint venture between ARAMCO and Mobil Investments. Techno lube is one of the leading lubricants manufacturer in UAE. CGT working together towards their Bulk Base Oil transportation from Shell, Sharlu, Universal Lubricants etc.</p>,<h2>Trotters Group – INNOVA Refining and Trading FZE</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/67a6cf56-1963-4eb7-a9ab-5b46b929f902.png" title="INNOVA">,<p>Established in the year 2010 as Trotters FZE is one of the emerging companies in UAE engaged in trading and reprocessing of petroleum and petro-chemical products. Providing tailors for transportation of Bulk Petrochemical products in ISO tanks.</p>,<h2>Asia Petro Chem</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ca2ba48e-da12-4a6b-8923-62fb44c95375.png" title="Asia Petro Chem">,<p>Based in RAK, UAE is one of the fastest growing name in Manufacturing, Distribution &amp; International Trade of Chemicals and Downstream Petrochemicals. Providing Bulk Road tankers and ISO tankers for the movements of Butanol, Ethanol, Xylene, Acetic Acid, Toluene etc all over UAE</p>,<h2>Gulf Petrochem's</h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0ae3451e-0cb2-42df-b216-40d46fde04b8.png" title="Gulf Petrochem&apos;s">,<p>Corporate Office is situated in United Arab Emirates (Hamriyah Free Zone, Sharjah) with global presence at several locations that inter alia includes India sub-continent, South East Asia, Africa, Europe and South America. Core activity includes Oil Trading &amp; Bunkering, Oil Refining, Grease Manufacturing, Oil Storage Terminals, Bitumen Manufacturing and Shipping &amp; Logistics. Supporting them by providing Bulk Bitumen tankers and Chemical tankers to transport Xylene, Toluene, Butanol etc.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://creektransport.com/we-at-creek-general-transport-give-our-customers-our-great/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d551d80c-0774-4148-b2ae-6a61d18160f6</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 14:08:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>